(Raj:)so I thought maybe
you could talk to her.
(Sheldon:)Of course.
What seems to be the trouble?
(Bernadette:)Something's wrong.
(Bernadette:)I don't care about
any of the baby stuff
(Bernadette:)every other mom is so into.
(Bernadette:)Honestly, I'm not even sure
I like babies.
(Dr Koothrapalli:)Look, some people are
baby people,
(Dr Koothrapalli:)and some people
are not baby people.
(Dr Koothrapalli:)It doesn't mean you won't
love your own baby.
(Bernadette:)But I thought I'd be
more excited.
(Dr Koothrapalli:)Oh, being excited
isn't a guarantee of anything.
(Dr Koothrapalli:)Rajesh's mother was thrilled
when she was pregnant with him.
(Dr Koothrapalli:)After he was born, she doted
on his every move.
(Dr Koothrapalli:)And you know what happened?
(Dr Koothrapalli:)He broke her heart,
moved halfway around the world,
(Dr Koothrapalli:)and dates only
poor white women.
(Dr Koothrapalli:)So you never know.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
I feel better now.
- I don't!
- Good.
(Dr Koothrapalli:)Bernadette, I hope
you have a daughter.